{
    "subject": "resource/Lais_Ribeiro",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "Model",
    "human_readable": "Lais Ribeiro is described as a Model.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9844456315040588,
            "question": "Is Lais Ribeiro a Model?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9678714871406555,
            "question": "Is Lais Ribeiro considered a successful model?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7470848560333252,
            "question": "What profession is Lais Ribeiro known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7351924180984497,
            "question": "What is Lais Ribeiro's background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6717327237129211,
            "question": "What are some of Lais Ribeiro's notable achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6458967328071594,
            "question": "Has Lais Ribeiro appeared in any magazines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6131473779678345,
            "question": "Where is Lais Ribeiro originally from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5960732698440552,
            "question": "In what industry does Lais Ribeiro work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5620530247688293,
            "question": "What brands has Lais Ribeiro worked with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5139890313148499,
            "question": "Has Lais Ribeiro walked the runway for famous designers?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lais Ribeiro is described as a Model.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2255_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What brands has Lais Ribeiro worked with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2255_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what industry does Lais Ribeiro work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2255_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Lais Ribeiro originally from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2255_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2255_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2255_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2255_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2255_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2255_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2255_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2255_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2255_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2255_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2255_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Lais Ribeiro is described as a Model. All of the documents mention her profession as a model, and some even specify her as a \"Brazilian fashion model\" or a \"Victoria's Secret Angel\", which are both models. Therefore, the value is \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents describe Lais Ribeiro as a Brazilian model, which supports the statement that she is described as a model."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}